Emmanuel TV Choir Christmas Carols
From The Manger Square In Bethlehem
I believe
Help my unbelief
Lord I believe
Help me overcome my unbelief
Believing is the only condition
For answered prayer
With my mouth I confess
And with my heart I believe
I believe God's Word
Is true for my life
Lord I believe
Help me overcome my unbelief
Don't let the devil
Get you out of faith
If you believe and do not doubt
Your faith takes over
Believing in Christ
That is my connection
I don't say amen
Because everyone says amen
But I say amen
Because I believe
Lord I believe
Help me overcome my unbelief
Believe is the only condition
Help my unbelief
RV: Mel Flowers 16/04/2019